[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Several actors were considered for the part of Roul Duke in Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas before Johnny Depp. Which of these is not among them?", "correct_answer": "Ed Harris", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Nicholson", "Dan Aykroyd", "John Malkovich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Risotto is made with special kinds of rice and is traditionally served with fish products or cheese. What country does this dish come from?", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Greece", "Portugal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Michael Keaton, George Cloony, Christian Bale, and Val Kilmer have all played the role of a super hero. Which is the hero?", "correct_answer": "Batman", "incorrect_answers": ["James Bond", "Superman", "Spider-Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately what percentage of humans have blood of the type Rh +?", "correct_answer": "85 %", "incorrect_answers": ["33 %", "35 %", "74 %"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the nickname of New York City?", "correct_answer": "The Big Apple", "incorrect_answers": ["Bogey and Bacall", "Stock Market City", "Rockefeller City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What biological term refers to the organs, whose function is considered to have been lost or reduced during evolution?", "correct_answer": "Vestigial organs", "incorrect_answers": ["Undeveloped organs", "Obsolete organs", "Stunted organs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to the fermented soybeans that are a part of the traditional Japanese breakfast?", "correct_answer": "Natto", "incorrect_answers": ["Congee", "Negi", "Youtiao"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Loudness is measured in decibels. A pneumatic drill at about 40 feet gives about 85 decibels. How many decibels result from an airplane taking off 200 feet (60 m) away?", "correct_answer": "120", "incorrect_answers": ["110", "300", "95"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This drink was invented for a party given by Winston Churchills mother.", "correct_answer": "The Manhattan", "incorrect_answers": ["The Gibson", "The Sidecar", "The Sloe Gin Fizz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was Billy from the movie St. Elmos Fire working, when Jules locked herself in her apartment?", "correct_answer": "a gas station", "incorrect_answers": ["a hair salon", "a car wash", "a fast food restaurant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To define someones personality, the Chinese consider this.", "correct_answer": "The year of birth", "incorrect_answers": ["The month of birth", "The time of birth", "The date of birth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which popular film directed by Bernardo Bertolucci portrays the life of an American widower?", "correct_answer": "Last Tango in Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["La Luna", "Stealing Beauty", "The Dreamers"]}]